<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<dataroot>
	<players>
		<person>
		    <name>Ryan Giggs</name>
		    <number>11</number>
		    <appearances>950</appearances>
		    <goals>168</goals>
		    <profileimage>giggs_profile</profileimage>
		    <mainimage>giggs</mainimage>  
		    <jerseyimage>giggs_jersey</jerseyimage>  
		    <url>http://www.manutd.com/en/Players-And-Staff/First-Team/Ryan-Giggs.aspx</url>
		    <position>Midfielder</position>
		    <description>
	        <summary>The Ryan Giggs story goes on - and on and on - and still his powers show no sign of waning. No longer the daring, dashing left-winger who tormented full-backs but a calming influence and one of the sharpest passers around.</summary>
	        <description>
Although his legs may have lost the explosive acceleration, his brain remains ahead of his younger rivals and his ability to produce telling crosses and assists has never been better. In summary, the Welshman is a phenomenon and a footballer to be treasured and talked about in revered tones long after he eventually decides to hang up his boots.

Bryan Robson feels that may not be until he has slipped into his 40s. A man who was not named PFA Players' Player until 2009 remains a key part of Sir Alex Ferguson's squad. An ally to the boss and an indvidual who commands total respect in the dressing room.

The most decorated player in the British game, the potential that earned him two PFA Young Player of the Year awards earlier in his career has long since been realised. Ryan is United's record appearance-maker; he surpassed Sir Bobby Charlton's 758 on the night he helped the Reds secure a third European Cup triumph - his second - in Moscow on 21 May 2008.</description>
	    </description>     
		</person>
		
		
		<person>
		    <name>David De Gea</name>
		    <number>1</number>
		    <appearances>96</appearances>
		    <goals>0</goals>
		    <profileimage>degea_profile</profileimage>
		    <mainimage>degea</mainimage>
		    <jerseyimage>degea_jersey</jerseyimage>   
		    <url>http://www.manutd.com/en/Players-And-Staff/First-Team/David-De-Gea.aspx</url>
		    <position>Goalkeeper</position>
		    <description>
	        <summary>David De Gea is a product of Atletico Madrid’s academy. Tall, athletic and confident with the ball, he progressed quickly through the youth ranks and spent his first professional season, 2008/09, with the club’s reserves. A first-team debut arrived early in the following term via a substitute appearance against FC Porto in the UEFA Champions League on 30 September 2009 - and thereafter he never looked back.</summary>
	        <description>
De Gea capped his maiden campaign in Atletico Madrid's first team by playing a major role in winning the UEFA Europa League - the club's first major European trophy in almost 50 years. 

His already burgeoning reputation was further enhanced during his second full season in La Liga and rumours of United's interest, which had first surfaced in January 2010, were more widely circulated when the Reds' then goalkeeping coach Eric Steele was seen scouting the youngster.

By the end of the 2010/11 season, David was widely touted by several media outlets as the primary choice to replace the retiring Edwin van der Sar at Old Trafford, although talks were put on hold whilst he helped Spain win UEFA’s Under-21 European Championship in Denmark. The transfer was completed after the tournament, on 29</description>
	    </description>     
		</person>
		
		<person>
		    <name>Rafael da Silva</name>
		    <number>2</number>
		    <appearances>138</appearances>
		    <goals>5</goals>
		    <profileimage>rafael_profile</profileimage>
		    <mainimage>rafael</mainimage>
		    <jerseyimage>rafael_jersey</jerseyimage>  
		    <url>http://www.manutd.com/en/Players-And-Staff/First-Team/Rafael.aspx</url>
		    <position>Right back</position>
		    <description>
	        <summary>Combining attacking ambition with defensive strength, Rafael da Silva is perhaps  the personification of the modern full-back.</summary>
	        <description>
The Brazilian starlet is already a full international, having excelled at United since making his first team debut during a 1-1 draw with Newcastle in August 2008 - a surprise outing that was prompted by an inspired display in Barry Fry's testimonial earlier in the month.

Incredibly, what made Rafa's bow even more impressive was the fact he hadn't played competitively in over a year while the Reds applied for international clearance on his (and twin brother Fabio) transfer from Fluminense.

With surpreme confidence and ambition, he made several noteworthy appearances thoughout the 2008/09 campaign, scoring his first goal at Arsenal in November before staking a claim for the full-time right-back berth ahead of Messrs Neville and Brown.

As a result, Sir Alex Ferguson soon offered a two-year contract extension and a nomination for the PFA Young Player of the Year award was soon won, as well as a place on the bench for the UEFA Champions League final defeat to Barcelona.    
	        </description>
	    </description>      
		</person>
		
		<person>
		    <name>Patrice Evra</name>
		    <number>3</number>
		    <appearances>348</appearances>
		    <goals>7</goals>
		    <profileimage>evra_profile</profileimage>
		    <mainimage>evra</mainimage>
		    <jerseyimage>evra_jersey</jerseyimage>  
		    <url>http://www.manutd.com/en/Players-And-Staff/First-Team/Patrice-Evra.aspx</url>
		    <position>Defender</position>
		    <description>
	        <summary>Patrice Evra has been incredibly consistent since arriving at Old Trafford in 2006, dominating the left-back position while regularly wearing the captain's armband in the absence of Nemanja Vidic. </summary>
	        <description>
The Frenchman's passionate persona has also made him a cult hero on the terraces and few will have felt more pride when the Reds reclaimed the Barclays Premier League at a canter in 2012/13 following the drama and heartbreak of the previous season.

United beat Liverpool, Arsenal and Inter Milan to Evra's signature in January 2006 when Sir Alex

Ferguson splashed the cash to shore up his defence, also bringing in the talismanic Vidic just a few days later.

Although only 24 at the time, Patrice had already been capped five times for France and was club captain at Monaco, where his reputation as an intelligent, attack-minded full-back had already been established.

In fact, he was a big success at the club, having won the 2003 French League Cup before reaching the 2004 UEFA Champions League final under manager Didier Deschamps, who was admittedly a big influence: "He transmitted to me the bug of winning at any price."</description>
	    </description>      
		</person>
		<person>
		    <name>Anderson</name>
		    <number>8</number>
		    <appearances>176</appearances>
		    <goals>9</goals>
		    <profileimage>anderson_profile</profileimage>
		    <mainimage>anderson</mainimage>
		    <jerseyimage>anderson_jersey</jerseyimage>  
		    <url>http://www.manutd.com/en/Players-And-Staff/First-Team/Anderson.aspx</url>
		    <position>Midfielder</position>
		    <description>
	        <summary>When Anderson arrived at Old Trafford from FC Porto in summer 2007 he wasn't exactly a household name. But after a wondrous debut season the Brazilian's talents became well known not just in Manchester, but around the world.</summary>
	        <description>
The early Ronaldinho comparisons were inevitable given both players began their careers at Brazilian side Gremio, who Anderson Luis de Abreu Oliveira (to give his full name) joined at the age of just five.

But that’s really where the similarities end. Where Ronaldinho is all flicks and flamboyance, Anderson (or Ando as he is known to his team-mates) is bustling with energy and possesses

an eye for a defence-splitting pass. He has skill and technical ability in abundance, but his preference for midfield combat could bring you to question his Brazilian roots (more so if you spotted his dancing after lifting the UEFA Champions League trophy in May 2008!)

At Gremio, Anderson made his first appearance aged just 16. He is most fondly remembered for a wonder goal against Nautico in November 2005, which earned a 1-0 win and promotion back to the top flight. He also earned a reputation internationally, shining with Brazil at the 2005 U17 World Cup, where he won the Adidas Golden Ball for most valuable player.</description>
	    	</description>      
		</person>
		<person>
		    <name>Michael Carrick</name>
		    <number>16</number>
		    <appearances>333</appearances>
		    <goals>21</goals>
		    <profileimage>carrick_profile</profileimage>
		    <mainimage>carrick</mainimage>
		    <jerseyimage>carrick_jersey</jerseyimage>  
		    <url>http://www.manutd.com/en/Players-And-Staff/First-Team/Michael-Carrick.aspx</url>
		    <position>Midfielder</position>
		    <description>
	        <summary>Michael Carrick has established himself as one of the most effective midfielders in the Barclays Premier League since his arrival from Tottenham Hotspur in 2006.</summary>
	        <description>
Understated, and often underrated, Carrick has become a lynchpin of the United engine room, dictating play with his considered, refined style.

In 2012/13 he gained wider acclaim for his performances, earning a spot in the PFA Premier League Team of the Season and being voted Players' Player of the Year by his United team-mates.

His influence on the Reds' squad was evident long before the 20th title-winning campaign, though. During his debut

campaign of 2006/07, he carved out a formidable partnership with Paul Scholes and began to mature into one of English football's most sophisticated and classy passing midfielders, quickly bagging the maiden honour of his professional career with the Premier League title.

A calming influence and the master of the interception, he also starred as the Reds conquered England and Europe in 2007/08, beating Chelsea to both the Premier League and Champions League before penning a new, four-ye</description>
	    	</description>      
		</person>
		<person>
		    <name>Jonny Evans</name>
		    <number>6</number>
		    <appearances>162</appearances>
		    <goals>5</goals>
		    <profileimage>evans_profile</profileimage>
		    <mainimage>evans</mainimage>
		    <jerseyimage>evans_jersey</jerseyimage>  
		    <url>http://www.manutd.com/en/Players-And-Staff/First-Team/Jonny-Evans.aspx</url>
		    <position>Defender</position>
		    <description>
	        <summary>When Anderson arrived at Old Trafford from FC Porto in summer 2007 he wasn't exactly a household name. But after a wondrous debut season the Brazilian's talents became well known not just in Manchester, but around the world.Belfast-born Jonny Evans is a tall and agile centre-back. An intelligent defender, he combines an uncompromising physical approach with the ability to pass the ball out from the back.</summary>
	        <description>
Jonny has risen through the United ranks to become an integral part of the first-team squad and 2011/12 was the season in which he truly came to the fore. The Northern Ireland international - who received his first call-up before he had even made his United debut - has blossomed into one of the best young defenders around.

Handed a Champions League squad number at the start of the 2005/06 season, aged just 17, Evans was a burgeoning talent

waiting to burst to prominence. Given his opportunity by the sale of Gerard Pique in the summer of 2008, Jonny did that during the course of the 2008/09 campaign.

Whenever called upon, Jonny's ice-cool calm is immediately apparent, even on huge stages like the San Siro or Stamford Bridge. His capacity for handling pressure is incredible, and stems partially from the extensive experience he gained out on loan.	</description>      	
			</description>      
		</person>
		<person>
		    <name>Rio Ferdinand</name>
		    <number>5</number>
		    <appearances>441</appearances>
		    <goals>8</goals>
		    <profileimage>ferdinand_profile</profileimage>
		    <mainimage>ferdinand</mainimage>
		    <jerseyimage>ferdinand_jersey</jerseyimage>  
		    <url>http://www.manutd.com/en/Players-And-Staff/First-Team/Rio-Ferdinand.aspx</url>
		    <position>Defender</position>
		    <description>
	        <summary>Armed with elegance, pace and an astute ability to read the game, Rio Ferdinand is one of the finest defenders in world football. </summary>
	        <description>
The Peckham-born star burst onto the scene with West Ham under the guidance of Harry Redknapp, later signing for Leeds in November 2000. However, the 2002 World Cup was Rio's real coming out party as his performances with England ultimately convinced Sir Alex Ferguson to part ways with an estimated £30million.

Now over 400 first-team appearances and countless trophies later, Ferdinand remains a giant of modern football and is widely regarded as one of the

finest defenders to have played on these shores.

Although his first season was initially hampered by injury, Rio became an integral player as United overtook Arsenal to claim the Barclays Premier League - capping a fine debut season in M16 for the new recruit.

However, in September 2003, disaster struck as Ferdinand missed a routine drugs test and was later banned from football for eight months, not returning until a 2-1 win over Liverpool in September 2004.</description>      	
			</description>      
		</person>
		<person>
		    <name>Javier Hernandez</name>
		    <number>14</number>
		    <appearances>126</appearances>
		    <goals>54</goals>
		    <profileimage>hernandez_profile</profileimage>
		    <mainimage>hernandez</mainimage>
		    <jerseyimage>hernandez_jersey</jerseyimage>  
		    <url>http://www.manutd.com/en/Players-And-Staff/First-Team/Javier-Hernandez.aspx</url>
		    <position>Striker</position>
		    <description>
		        <summary>Javier 'Chicharito' Hernandez enjoyed a wonderful maiden season for United in 2010/11, scoring 20 goals in all competitions and terrorising defences with his pace and movement.</summary>
		        <description>
Adored in his native Mexico, it wasn't long before he also became a fans' favourite in the UK, thanks to his footballing ability, friendly demeanour and dedicated professionalism.

Chicha completed his move to Old Trafford in July 2010, becoming United’s first Mexican player. He joined from hometown club Chivas de Guadalajara, for whom he had scored 29 goals in 79 games since making his debut as a teenager in 2006.

Unusually for a club of United's stature, the transfer was conducted completely under the radar: only the player and his father were aware of the deal and there was no prior speculation in the media, either in the UK or Mexico.

'Chicharito' means ‘little pea’ and Hernandez attracted the moniker because he’s the son of Javier Hernandez, himself a top Mexican striker who played in the 1986 World Cup and was nicknamed 'Chicharo' ('pea') because of his green eyes.
				</description>      	
			</description>      
		</person>
		<person>
		    <name>Nani</name>
		    <number>17</number>
		    <appearances>222</appearances>
		    <goals>40</goals>
		    <profileimage>nani_profile</profileimage>
		    <mainimage>nani</mainimage>
		    <jerseyimage>nani_jersey</jerseyimage>  
		    <url>http://www.manutd.com/en/Players-And-Staff/First-Team/Nani.aspx</url>
		    <position>Winger</position>
		    <description>
		        <summary>Luís Carlos Almeida da Cunha - or Nani, as we all know him - is a powerful, pacy winger capable of dominating matches with his unique brand of wing wizardry.</summary>
		        <description>
Since signing from Sporting Lisbon in 2007, the Portuguese has become an integral player at Old Trafford, moving out of Cristiano Ronaldo's looming shadow to become a star in his own right.

His debut season is hard to beat, having won the title and European Cup, though the 2010/11 campaign is widely considered his 'coming of age' term. After helping the Reds seal a record-breaking 19th title, he then took home

the Player of the Year prize at United's annual awards night, an accolade that was more than deserved.

Sir Alex Ferguson highlighted an increased maturity in the wide man and his blossoming personality. And it seemed fair to suggest that the inconsistency that had, at times, frustrated fans earlier in his career was now a by-product of youth.

But the winger would not stop there, though. His close control, tight turning circle and acute spatial awareness were sharper than ever during his fifth season in M16 and few defenders could get anywhere near him - on either flank.
				</description>      	
			</description>      
		</person>
		<person>
		    <name>Wayne Rooney</name>
		    <number>10</number>
		    <appearances>416</appearances>
		    <goals>204</goals>
		    <profileimage>rooney_profile</profileimage>
		    <mainimage>rooney</mainimage>
		    <jerseyimage>rooney_jersey</jerseyimage>  
		    <url>http://www.manutd.com/en/Players-And-Staff/First-Team/Wayne-Rooney.aspx</url>
		    <position>Striker</position>
		    <description>
		        <summary>Wayne Rooney is one of only 25 players to have made 400 appearances for Manchester United – and he became the fourth youngest Red to reach that milestone in April 2013.</summary>
		        <description>
The striker burst onto the Old Trafford stage in September 2004, netting an unforgettable hat-trick against Fenerbahce on his debut.

Perhaps his performance wasn't that surprising, given the enormous pedigree he had amassed since making a lasting impression on now-Academy manager Paul McGuiness some years previous. In an Under-9 match between United and Everton, McGuiness remembers. “Rooney scored the perfect bicycle kick,

which for a kid of eight or nine years old was really something special." It merely hinted at what was to follow and, of course, it was a trick he would repeat on the biggest of stages in the Manchester derby, netting a goal that will be repeated forever more.
				</description>      	
			</description>      
		</person>
		<person>
		    <name>Chris Smalling</name>
		    <number>12</number>
		    <appearances>96</appearances>
		    <goals>3</goals>
		    <profileimage>smalling_profile</profileimage>
		    <mainimage>smalling</mainimage>
		    <jerseyimage>smalling_jersey</jerseyimage>  
		    <url>http://www.manutd.com/en/Players-And-Staff/First-Team/Chris-Smalling.aspx</url>
		    <position>Defender</position>
		    <description>
		        <summary>With great pace, power and intelligence, Chris Smalling remains the heir apparant to Rio Ferdinand in the role of ball-playing centre-back.</summary>
		        <description>
Incredibly, just 18 months after arriving at Fulham from non-league Maidstone, defender Chris Smalling agreed to terms that would make him a Manchester United player from 1 July 2010.

His first campaign at Old Trafford went better than anyone could have expected and, having been given chances to impress in various competitions, namely the UEFA Champions League and League Cup, he looked completely at home in M16.

An injury to mentor Ferdinand

ultimately proved beneficial as Smalling enjoyed an extended run in the team, contributing to his impressive tally of 33 first-team appearances. Of course, a title winners' medal was also earned during an impressive debut campaign.

The defender's impressive exploits were later rewarded with a new five-year deal, which was signed in July 2011 ahead of a promising start to his second term with the champions, which was largely spent at right-back while Rafael was sidelined through injury.
				</description>      	
			</description>      
		</person>
		<person>
		    <name>Robin van Persie</name>
		    <number>20</number>
		    <appearances>61</appearances>
		    <goals>39</goals>
		    <profileimage>vanpersie_profile</profileimage>
		    <mainimage>vanpersie</mainimage>
		    <jerseyimage>vanpersie_jersey</jerseyimage>  
		    <url>http://www.manutd.com/en/Players-And-Staff/First-Team/Robin-van-Persie.aspx</url>
		    <position>Striker</position>
		    <description>
		        <summary>All United fans will remember where they were when news broke that a deal had been agreed with Arsenal to bring Robin van Persie to Old Trafford and he put pen-to-paper on Friday 17 August 2012, and no Red will ever forget the incredible campaign that followed.</summary>
		        <description>
A year after scooping the PFA Player of the Year and the Football Writers' Footballer of the Year prizes after a fabulous season with the Gunners, United's no.20 was picking up his first title winners' medal having played a huge part in securing, rather aptly, title no.20 for the Reds.

The Dutchman also claimed the league's Golden Boot after

netting 26 times - he fired 30 goals overall, was voted the Sir Matt Busby Way Player of the Year and collected the Goal of Season accolade at United's annual awards dinner for his incredible volley against Aston Villa in April 2013, the second goal of his hat-trick in the game that clinched the Championship crown.

Born in Rotterdam, he really made his mark at local side Feyenoord and was chased by some of England's top clubs after a couple of seasons impressing on the left wing. Despite rumoured interest from Tottenham, Arsenal snapped him up for £2.75million in 2004 and he soon proved value for money.
				</description>      	
			</description>      
		</person>
		<person>
		    <name>Nemanja Vidic</name>
		    <number>15</number>
		    <appearances>278</appearances>
		    <goals>19</goals>
		    <profileimage>vidic_profile</profileimage>
		    <mainimage>vidic</mainimage>
		    <jerseyimage>vidic_jersey</jerseyimage>  
		    <url>http://www.manutd.com/en/Players-And-Staff/First-Team/Nemanja-Vidic.aspx</url>
		    <position>Defender</position>
		    <description>
		        <summary>Tall, uncompromising and solid as a rock: Nemanja Vidic is the epitome of what a Manchester United captain should aspire to. </summary>
		        <description>
Relentless in the tackle and formidable in the air, the Serbian powerhouse has become one of the Premier League’s most-feared defenders and a key factor in United's recent silverware haul.

Vida, as he's affectionately known, began his career with boyhood club Red Star Belgrade, joining their youth programme at 14. His first-team debut didn't arrive until 2001 but he went on to make 22 appearances in his first season.

His stay with Red Star ended with a domestic league and cup double before switching to Russian outfit Spartak Moscow in August 2004. Just 39 games and four goals later, United came calling and the Reds announced his signing on Christmas Day, 2005.

Without a game in two months, due to the Russian season's early climax, Nemanja took some time to shine but after finding his feet, began to show his unquestionable class. Unfortunately, a collarbone injury sustained at the end of March 2007 kept him out of the title run-in, but his performances had already inspired a rousing song from the fans.
				</description>      	
			</description>      
		</person>
		<person>
		    <name>Danny Welbeck</name>
		    <number>19</number>
		    <appearances>112</appearances>
		    <goals>22</goals>
		    <profileimage>welbeck_profile</profileimage>
		    <mainimage>welbeck</mainimage>
		    <jerseyimage>welbeck_jersey</jerseyimage>  
		    <url>http://www.manutd.com/en/Players-And-Staff/First-Team/Danny-Welbeck.aspx</url>
		    <position>Forward</position>
		    <description>
		        <summary>Having worked his way through the ranks at United, Danny Welbeck established himself as a first-team regular of real talent in 2011/12 and he played an important role in helpinng the Reds scoop title no.20 in 2012/13.</summary>
		        <description>
The Manchester-born frontman joined United's youth set-up in summer 2007 and quickly caught the eye with his skilful, strong and pacy displays.

As a schoolboy, Welbeck played a prominent role in the Under-18s’ run to the 2006/07 FA Youth Cup final. He bagged nine goals in 14 starts for the Academy in 2007/08 and seven goals in 11 starts for the Reserves, including a superb hat-trick

against Manchester City, as the Reds' second string won both the Manchester and Lancashire Senior Cups.

His performances earned him a call-up to the first-team squad for United's winter trip to Saudi Arabia. Although he missed a last-minute penalty, Welbeck impressed in his 25-minute appearance against Al Hilal. Capable of playing out wide as well as up front, he was later named on the substitutes' bench for the Champions League semi-final second leg against Barcelona and was part of the travelling party for the final in Moscow.
				</description>      	
			</description>      
		</person>
		<person>
		    <name>Ashley Young</name>
		    <number>18</number>
		    <appearances>64</appearances>
		    <goals>8</goals>
		    <profileimage>young_profile</profileimage>
		    <mainimage>young</mainimage>
		    <jerseyimage>young_jersey</jerseyimage>  
		    <url>http://www.manutd.com/en/Players-And-Staff/First-Team/Ashley-Young.aspx</url>
		    <position>Winger</position>
		    <description>
		        <summary>Since arriving from Aston Villa in 2011, Ashley Young has almost seemlessly adapted to life at Old Trafford to become a formidable attacking weapon for Manchester United.</summary>
		        <description>
Although his first season in M16 ultimately ended in disappointment - with rivals Manchester City stealing the title on the final day - there were plenty of individual highlights for the England international, most notably a couple of doubles against Spurs and Arsenal.

A much-deserved England call-up for Euro 2012 soon followed and, after years of climbing the ladder, the tricky winger had

finally reached the higher echelons of football.

Of course, his career had been on an upward curve for some time. At Watford, where he was once on the brink of being released, Young became an integral player and eventually caught the interest of high-flying Aston Villa in 2007.

The fee, rising to almost £10million, was declared steep by those supposedly in the know - but it soon looked a bargain. Flourishing at Villa Park, he won the 2009 PFA Young Player of the Year award and was declared 'world class' by manager Martin O'Neill.
				</description>      	
			</description>      
		</person>
		
	</players>
</dataroot>
